Anirudh Srinath Belwadi

Maharashtra, India



anirudh.belwadi@gmail.com



+919892348079



linkedin.com/in/anirudh-srinath-belwadi

Summary

Engineer | Musician | Singer | Social Activist

The raison d'être of my life is to be determined towards the software world and its development for the betterment in the standard of living of the society.

Music has been a part my of life since childhood and will be swan song. It has edified me and gifted me a 'Never Give Up!' attitude in life. I have learnt to play several instruments of which I have mastered Keyboard and Guitar. I still stay motivated to achieve a good command on new instruments.

Additionally, I possess a good experience in Python, JAVA, JS, HTML, CSS, SQL.

Experience



Full Stack Developer

HaleAl

Apr 2020 - Present (7 months +)

HaleAl aims to provide assistance for faster and more accurate diagnosis in the healthcare industry using artificial intelligence



Administrator

Developer Student Clubs

Aug 2020 - Present (3 months +)

- Facilitator for "30 days of Google Cloud Program"



Core Team Member

TEDxSIESGST

Jul 2019 - Present (1 year 4 months +)



STES Media Volunteer

SIES GST Students' Council

Sep 2020 - Present (2 months +)



Photographer

AB Photography

May 2019 - Present (1 year 6 months +)



Full stack intern

HaleAl

Mar 2020 - Apr 2020 (2 months)

HaleAl aims to provide assistance for faster and more accurate diagnosis in the healthcare industry using artificial intelligence

Education



University of Mumbai

Bachelor of Engineering - BE, Computer Engineering 2018 - 2022 Aaroha (Music club)



Vasant Vihar High School & Junior College, Thane

High School Education, Science 2008 - 2018

Licenses & Certifications



MyCaptain - Python Programming - Indian Institute of Management Bangalore



Introduction to Amazon S3 - Amazon Web Services (AWS)



Amazon S3 Primer - Amazon Web Services (AWS)



AWS Builders Online Series - Amazon Web Services (AWS)



Skill Badges in GCP - Qwiklabs

Skills

Full-Stack Development • Python (Programming Language) • Piano Playing • Web Development • Web Design • Music • Singing • Guitar Playing • HTML5 • HTML

Honors & Awards



Sanskriti Gaurav Puraskar - Sanskriti Academy of Fine Arts, Thane, Maharashtra Oct 2018

The Sanskriti Gaurav Puraskar is awarded every in the annual program of Sanskriti Academy of Fine Arts, Thane for the most deserving student of the academy who excels in more than one art form. I was awarded for transcending in my art forms of learning Keyboard and Guitar. The Director of this academy also mentioned my contribution towards the Kerala Flood Relief Drive that year.

Cerificate and Citation - https://drive.google.com/open?id=15-Elpmne1p6bXy-iBGBTyJJFf8kL1to9 Sanskriti Academy of Fine Arts - https://www.facebook.com/groups/Sanskritiacademy/

Sanskriti Yogya Puraskar for Keyboard and Guitar - Sanskriti Academy of Fine Arts, Thane, Maharashtra

Oct 2018

The Sanskriti Gaurav Puraskar is awarded every year in the annual program of Sanskriti Academy of Fine Arts, Thane for the student who excels in a particular art form. I was awarded for outdoing in my art forms of learning Keyboard and Guitar.

Certificate and Citation - https://drive.google.com/open?id=153XwOg5OwmKJRqkeIh4i5mJaVM-3c0IZ Sanskriti Academy of Fine Arts - https://www.facebook.com/groups/Sanskritiacademy/

Runnerup in Intercollegiate Quiz - MATRIX - SIES Graduate School of Technology Sep 2018

Matrix is an inter-collegiate Quiz competition conducted by SIES Graduate School of Technology every year in their technical fest 'Cognition'. This is a pre-fest event consisting of 5 rounds where you are exposed to both curricular quiz and also fun rounds.

Runnerup in Tug of War - SIES Graduate School of Technology Feb 2020

Stood 2nd in the Tug of War event of TML (TML - Tattva Moksha Lakshya - Annual technical, cultural and sports fest of SIES Graduate School of Technology). Lead a team of 10, who expressed great teamwork and made it to the finals.

Most Enterprising Student in FE - SIES Graduate School of Technology Mar 2019

"An enterprising person is one who sees opportunity in all areas of life". I have always been an enthusiastic person in taking up challenging tasks and participating in various events and projects of diverse domains.